[
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "Which of the following git command that downloads your repository from GitHub to your local machine?",
		"options": ["git fork", "git push", "git rebase", "git clone"],
		"answer": 3,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Definition",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "Git is a",
		"options": [
			"Distributed version control system",
			"Localized version control system",
			"Centralized version control system",
			"None of the above"
		],
		"answer": 0,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "Which of the following git command can be used to check the stored stashes?",
		"options": [
			"git stash branch",
			"git stash list",
			"git stash",
			"git stash show"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"difficulty": "Medium"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "Which is used to reference cloned remote repository?",
		"options": ["head", "origin", "log", "status"],
		"answer": 1,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "Git log command contains:",
		"options": [
			"commit message",
			"commit date and author metadata",
			"commit hash",
			"all of the above"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "git fetch + git merge equal to?",
		"options": [
			"git push",
			"git stash",
			"git pull",
			"git checkout"
		],
		"answer": 2,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "Looking at the following commands, describe what is happening. git checkout feature-user-location git cherry-pick kj2342134sdf090093f0sdgasdf99sdfo992mmmf9921231",
		"options": [
			"The commit is being tagged for release on the feature-user-location branch",
			"A commit is being copied from its original branch over to the feature-user-location branch",
			"The commit is being cherry picked as the new HEAD of the commit history",
			"The branch is switched to the feature-user-location branch, and the specified commit is applied to the branch."
		],
		"answer": 2,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "Your team lead needs a list of all commits that will be moved before you perform a rebase. Which command can you use to access that information?",
		"options": [
			"git rebase -log",
			"git rebase -i",
			"git rebase -verbose",
			"git rebase -all"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"difficulty": "Medium"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "While modifying a file, you're unexpectedly assigned an urgent bug fix on another branch. How can you temporarily save your local work without committing?",
		"options": [
			"This is not possible, as you cannot save locally without committing.",
			"Run git hold to save a local copy of what you're doing to return to later.",
			"Save your work with git local-cache.",
			"Use git stash to save your work and come back later and reapply the stashed commit."
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "What is an alternative to merging in git?",
		"options": ["Basing", "Rebasing", "Squashing", "None of these"],
		"answer": 1,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "What does refs in git store?",
		"options": [
			"SHA-1 value", 
			"Random Number", 
			"Date and Time Stamp", 
			"None of the above"
		],
		"answer": 0,
		"difficulty": "Medium"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "What option can you use to apply git configurations across your entire git environment?",
		"options": ["--all", "--global", "-master", "--globe"],
		"answer": 1,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "What does the git stash drop command do?",
		"options": [
			"deletes the stash", 
			"lists everything in the stash", 
			"throws away the oldest entry", 
			"removes the most recent stash entry"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "What command would let you modify your previous commit?",
		"options": ["--quickfix", "-modify", "--fix", "-amend"],
		"answer": 3,
		"difficulty": "Medium"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "What does the following command do to the git repository? git reset--soft HEAD",
		"options": [
			"It sets HEAD to the previous commit and leaves changes from the undone commit in the stage/index.",
			"It resets the working branch to the first commit", 
			"It deletes all previous commits and reset the repository history back to its initial state", 
			"None of the above"
		],
		"answer": 0,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "What command creates a new branch from the currently checked-out branch?",
		"options": [
			"git-b checkout", 
			"git checkout-b", 
			"git checkout", 
			"git branch"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "What is the meaning of remote repository in Git?",
		"options": [
			"a version of the repository that mirrors changes made in the local repository's master branch for open-source collaboration efforts", 
			"the lead repository elected by the Git arbitrator found within local repositories of collaborating team members", 
			"a read-only version of the repository stored on a backup server in case local repositories become lost or corrupted", 
			"a version of the repository hosted on the internet or network that is pushed to or pulled from by collaborators"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "Which file in a git repository specifies intentionally untracked files that git should ignore?",
		"options": [".gitignore", ".git-exclude", ".gitexclude", ".git-ignore"],
		"answer": 0,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	},
	{
		"topic": "Git",
		"subtopic": "Command",
		"type": "MCQ",
		"question": "What is the command for switching branches?",
		"options": [
			"git switch <branch name>", 
			"git checkout <branch name>", 
			"git branch <branch name>", 
			"git move <branch name>"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"difficulty": "Easy"
	}
]
